<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>WiseTech Inc - Blog</title>
  <updated>2021-08-17T14:23:57-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>WiseTech Inc</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/5-reasons-you-should-get-surveillance-cameras-for-your-home-and-business</id>
    <published>2021-08-17T14:23:57-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-08-17T14:34:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/5-reasons-you-should-get-surveillance-cameras-for-your-home-and-business"/>
    <title>5 Reasons You Should Get Surveillance Cameras For Your Home And Business</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mo Waez</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Surveillance cameras are useful for a number of reasons. The first and foremost is security. Even if you don’t think you need these cameras, the moment you do buy security cameras from shops like Arlo for your home and business, you will feel relieved. If you still need that extra push to buy surveillance cameras, let’s take a look at 5 reasons you must.</p>
<p><strong>1 . Deters Theft</strong><br>If home and business have surveillance cameras, that is security in itself. The presence of it lets any potential thief know that if they were to attempt to steal anything, they could be recognized through the security footage. If the security footage is being watched in real-time, they would be caught immediately. <br><br>You would also notice suspicious attempts beforehand. If someone is walking aimlessly outside your house for days, it should be a first warning sign. Surveillance cameras also discourage shoplifters.</p>
<p><strong>2. Activity tracker</strong><br>You can check when your employees are coming in to work and when they are leaving. This also applies to your home; you can check if your domestic worker is performing his or her duties as expected. The presence of security cameras would also encourage them to work harder in general. If the security cameras are hidden from view and they are unaware of it, you can determine how serious they are about their work.</p>
<p><strong>3. Recording Evidence</strong><br>On the off chance that thievery does occur, you would have security footage to determine who stole your possessions and when. This is a great way for businesses to retrieve any lost paperwork. Later, in court, footage from security cameras could also be used as evidence.</p>
<p><strong>4. Improves Workplace Safety</strong><br>You can keep track of all that your employees are doing. From the security footage, you can see if there are conflicts among the employees through their body language- even if you can’t hear what they are talking about. You can make sure that everyone behaves appropriately and conducts themselves in a professional manner. As pointed out before, the mere presence of security cameras deters employees from behaving in a way that’s unbecoming of them.</p>
<p><strong>5. Checking How Your Family Is Doing</strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1453/7046/files/Arlo_Kids_-_Copy_160x160.jpg?v=1629222947" alt="" style="float: right;"></p>
<p>If you have kids at home, smart surveillance cameras allow you to check the live security footage from anywhere. You could be at work and still see how your pets or your children are doing at home. It is natural to feel anxious about your family, even if there are caretakers. So, the presence of security cameras is reassuring and should help you focus better on work.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Final Thoughts<br></strong>There are many different types of surveillance cameras in the market. Their price range also varies, allowing you to find one that’s tailored to your needs. For your home, we would recommend Essentials Indoor Camera from Arlo as it comes with a privacy shield. When you are at home, you can close the privacy shutter and disable the audio with simple clicks to get total privacy. There are also other types such as Ultra 2 Spotlight for outside surveillance. The cameras from Arlo come with an internet connection, HD vision, night vision, Bluetooth connection, and weather protection, which makes it the best choice.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/free-shipping</id>
    <published>2021-07-05T14:37:38-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-06T13:26:02-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/free-shipping"/>
    <title>Free Shipping</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mo Waez</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>To all our valued customers. </p>
<p>We wouldn't have been here serving you without your support.  We always try to find the best prices and products to offer.  Your stratification is our highest priority.</p>
<p>That is why we're happy to announce we've lowered <span>our minimum purchase price for free shipping.  Any order $50 or more will qualify for free shipping.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p>We're always try to find new ways to save you money and offer more services.  If you have any questions, or concerns please <a href="https://wisetech.ca/pages/contact-us" title="WiseTech - Contact Us.">contact us</a>.</p>
<p>Thank you</p>
<p>WiseTech Team</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/offering-a-new-interest-free-payment-plan-to-our-customers</id>
    <published>2021-05-25T15:52:10-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-25T15:52:10-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/offering-a-new-interest-free-payment-plan-to-our-customers"/>
    <title>Offering a New Interest Free Payment Plan to Our Customers</title>
    <author>
      <name>Razan Waez</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At WiseTech not only do we offer the best prices for our customers, but we always try to find new ideas and services that can help our customers as well. That is why we are happy to announce we will be providing a new payment plan service.  The payment plan service from <a href="https://paybright.com/en/" target="_blank" title="PayBright Website" rel="noopener noreferrer">PayBright</a> will allow you to divide your payment and make 4 bi-weekly payments, interest free. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To use this service, prior to completing the purchase at the checkout, select PayBright as the method of payment and click on Complete Order. A new webpage for PayBright will open prompting you to complete the payment.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have any questions about PayBright, you can contact <a href="https://help.paybright.com/hc/en-us" title="PayBright Customer Service" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PayBright customer service</a> and they will answer all your questions.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">WiseTech Team</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/audio-technica-vs-sennheiser-wireless-bluetooth-over-ear-headphones</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:40:42-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T17:19:15-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://wisetech.ca/blogs/news/audio-technica-vs-sennheiser-wireless-bluetooth-over-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Audio-Technica vs. Sennheiser - Wireless Bluetooth Over-Ear Headphones</title>
    <author>
      <name>Razan Waez</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p> </p>
<p><b>Audio-Technica Wireless Bluetooth Over-Ear Headphones - Black (ATH-M50xBT)<br></b><a href="https://wisetech.ca/products/audio-technica-wireless-bluetooth-over-ear-headphones-black-ath-m50xbt" target="_blank" title="Audio-Technica Wireless Bluetooth Over-Ear Headphones - Black (ATH-M50xBT)" rel="noopener noreferrer">View Product</a></p>
<div style="text-align: right;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1453/7046/files/a3d02a7e8fcafa0ed32f547fdaa8ebc0_240x240.jpg?v=1621457202" alt="Audio-Technica Wireless Bluetooth Over-Ear Headphones - Black (ATH-M50xBT)" style="float: right;" width="240x240" height="240x240"></div>
<ul>
<li><span>Great for Video Editing</span></li>
<li><span>On the higher end of sound clarity compared to other headphones</span></li>
<li><span>Can be used as wireless or plugged in</span></li>
<li><span><span>Includes carrying bag to store headphones</span></span></li>
<li><span>2 Cables (3.5 mm aux cable &amp; micro USB charger)</span></li>
<li>
<span><span>Metal headband - stretchable and bendable </span></span>
<div style="text-align: right;"></div>
</li>
<li><span>Ear pads can be changed if there is wear and tear through the years</span></li>
<li><span>Comfortable cushion on the ear pads</span></li>
</ul>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><b>Sennheiser Over-Ear Noise Cancelling Bluetooth Headphones - Black/Red<br></b><a href="https://wisetech.ca/products/sennheiser-over-ear-noise-cancelling-bluetooth-headphones-black-red" target="_blank" title="Sennheiser Over-Ear Noise Cancelling Bluetooth Headphones - Black/Red" rel="noopener noreferrer">View Product</a><b><br></b></p>
<div style="text-align: right;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1453/7046/files/90a2ca4f85d159a894bc4aaba2808643_240x240.jpg?v=1621457432" alt="Sennheiser Over-Ear Noise Cancelling Bluetooth Headphones - Black/Red" style="float: right;"></div>
<ul>
<li><span>Much more affordable than other headphones</span></li>
<li><span>Bendable and stretchable for easy storage</span></li>
<li><span>Includes carrying bag to store headphones</span></li>
<li><span>Includes charging cable</span></li>
<li><span>Strong BlueTooth strength</span></li>
<li>
<span><span>Excellent Noise cancellation </span></span>
<div style="text-align: right;"></div>
</li>
<li><span>Ear pads can be changed if there is wear and tear through the years</span></li>
<li><span>Tight on the ears - but will loosen after 4-5 uses</span></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><span>Thank you for reading. Don’t forget to check back regularly for a new blog. </span></p>
<p><span>Thank you for shopping at WiseTech - Where Your Dreams Come True - Be WISE, Shop WISELY</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
